Finding Aid for the CBS Inc. Film and Television Collection PASC-M.0072
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Movies, Series 5.
  - The Other Woman -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 131.
    Plot: After losing his wife of 28 years in a skiing accident, widower Lou Chadway (Hal Linden) falls for and marries his daughter's sexy roomate but soon learns that he has absolutely nothing in common with her. Peg Gilford (Anne Meara) is a divorced grandmother who comes along to take Lou's mind off her and they embark on a secret love affair.
    - Logs 3192-3198, 11/16/1982; open reel audio tape (Box 1034, Folder 2)
      On container, "CED/11-16-82/R140/Logs 3192-3198/"Other Woman" Pre-Score."
    - Logs 3192-3198, 11/16/1982; 1 in. tape (Box 1038, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/11-16-82/R93/Logs 3192-3198/Other Woman/Pre-score."
    - Log 3395, 02/22/1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1081, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/2-22-83/R110DD/Logs 3395 DD2/"Other Woman"."
    - Logs 3373-3390, 02/18/1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1081, Folder 15)
      On container, "CED/2-18-83/R152/Logs 3373-3390/"Other Woman"."
    - Logs 3465-378, 2/22/83; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 17)
      On container, "CED/2-22-83/R109B/Logs 3465-3478 + DD 1-10 (Vocal Track Only)/Other Woman."
    - Logs 3431-3464, 2/22/83; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 18)
      On container, "CED/2-22-83/R108/Logs 3431-3464/Other Woman."
    - Logs 3465-3474, 2/22/83; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 19)
      On container, "CED/2-22-83/R109ADD/Logs 3465-3474 + DD 1-10 (Orchestra Only)/Other Woman."
    - Logs 3391-3430, 02/18/1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1089, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/2-18-83/R107/Logs 3391-3430/"Other Woman"."
    - Logs 3391-3430, 02/18/1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1109, Folder 16)
      On container, "CED/2-18-83/R153/LOGS 3391-3430/"Other Woman"."
    - Logs 3431-3464, 02/22/1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1112, Folder 7)
      On container, "CED/2-22-83/R154/LOGS 3431-3464/"Other Woman"."
    - Logs 3465-3478, 02/22/1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1112, Folder 8)
      On container, "CED/2-22-83/R155+DD/LOGS 3465-3478+DD1-10/"Other Woman"."
    - Log 3395, 02/22/1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1112, Folder 9)
      On container, "CED/2-22-83/R156 DD/LOG 3395 DD2/"Other Woman"."
  - Outback Bound -- Papers, Subseries 132.
    Production no. 0310-3562-0101. Plot: A girl from Beverly Hills tries to find her fathers opal mine in the Australian outback.
    - Post Production Schedule no. 3, 1988 August 25; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 16)
  - Outback Bound -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 133.
    Production no. 0310-3562-0101.
    - Logs 8221-8237, September 23, 1988; open reel audio tape (Box 1065, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/9-23-88/R388/Logs 8221-8237/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8238-8273, September 23, 1988; open reel audio tape (Box 1065, Folder 16)
      On container, "CBS/9-23-88/R398/Logs 8238-8273/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8238-8273, September 23, 1988; open reel audio tape (Box 1065, Folder 17)
      On container, "CBS/9-23-88/R370/Logs 8238-8273/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8221-8237, September 23, 1988; open reel audio tape (Box 1065, Folder 18)
      On container, "CBS/9-23-88/R369/Logs 8221-8237/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8201-8220, September 23, 1988; open reel audio tape (Box 1065, Folder 19)
      On container, "CBS/9-23-88/R368/Logs 8201-8220/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8154-8188, September 22,1988; open reel audio tape (Box 1079, Folder 14)
      On container, "CBS/9-22-88/R366/Logs 8154-8188/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8189-8200, September 22, 1988; open reel audio tape (Box 1079, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/9-22-88/R367/Logs 8189-8200/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8154-8188, September 22, 1988; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1079, Folder 16)
      On container, "CBS/9-22-88/R385/Logs 8154-8188/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8189-8200, September 22, 1988; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1080, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS/9-22-88/R386/Logs 8189-8200/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
    - Logs 8201-8220, September 23, 1988; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1080, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS/9-23-88/R387/Logs 8201-8220/"Outback Bound" Miles Goodman."
  - Penalty Phase -- Papers, Subseries 134.
    - Cast and Production Credits, 1986 October 21; 2 pages (Box 1860, Folder 17)
    - Movies on the CBS Television Network Notice, 1986 October 20; 3 pages (Box 1860, Folder 17)
      Description of the CBS Tuesday movie selection.
  - Picking Up the Pieces -- Papers, Subseries 135.
    Plot: A sheltered wife (Margot Kidder) of a surgeon (David Ackroyd) suddenly finds herself thrust into the middle of a messy divorce. Also known as "First Strike on Sycamore Lane.")
    - Post Production Schedule no. 3, 1985 April 12; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 17)
  - Picking Up the Pieces -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 136.
    - Logs 5158-5184, June 6, 1985; 1/4" tape (Box 1093, Folder 6)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R233/logs 5158-5184/"Picking up the Pieces"."
    - Logs 5129-5157, June 3, 1985; 1/4" tape (Box 1093, Folder 7)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R232/logs 5129-5157/"Picking up the Pieces"."
    - Logs 5092-5108, June 3, 1985; 1/2" tape (Box 1093, Folder 8)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R180/logs 5092-5108/"Picking up the Pieces"."
    - Logs 5109-5128, June 3, 1985; 1/2" tape (Box 1093, Folder 9)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R181/logs 5109-5128/"Picking up the Pieces"."
    - Logs 5129-5157, June 3, 1985; 1/2" tape (Box 1093, Folder 10)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R182/logs 5129-5157/"Picking up the Pieces"."
    - Logs 5158-5184, June 3, 1985; 1/2" tape (Box 1093, Folder 11)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R183/logs 5158-5184/"Picking up the Pieces"."
    - Logs 5109-5128, June 3, 1985; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1130, Folder 17)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R231/LOGS 5109-5128/"Picking Up The Pieces"."
    - Logs 5092-5108, June 3, 1985; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1130, Folder 18)
      On container, "CED/6-3-85/R230/LOGS 5092-5108/"Picking Up The Pieces"."
    - [Contents Unidentified], February 25, 1985; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1153, Folder 7)
      On container, "CED/2-25-85/Nagra Playbacks/"Picking Up The Pieces"/First Strike Westchester Prod./Roll 2X/Wild Sound/Protection/Piano Music."
    - [Contents Unidentified], February 25, 1985; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1153, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/2-25-85/Nagra Playbacks/"Picking Up The Pieces"/First Strike."
    - [Contents Unidentified], February 25, 1985; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1153, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified Sound Recordings, 6 3" open reel audio tapes (Box 1830)
      On envelope, "Picking Up the Pieces." On boxes, "Moonlight Becomes You;" Stan Getz "I Was Doin' All Right;" Scott Hamilton "These Foolish Things," "Everything Happens to Me."
  - The Pirate Movie -- Papers, Subseries 137.
    Plot: The crew of a large ship sail the high seas encountering other pirates from other ships.
    - Movies on the CBS Television Network Notice, 1986 July 18; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 17)
      Description of the film starring Kristy McNichol and Christopher Atkins to be broadcast on August 15, 1986.
  - Playhouse 90 -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 138.
    - [Contents Unidentified], open reel audio tape (Box 1033, Folder 5)
      On container, "PH 90/Music II."
    - [Contents Unidentified], open reel audio tape (Box 1033, Folder 7)
      On container, "PH 90/Music I."
    - Theme, open reel audio tape (Box 1033, Folder 8)
      On container, "Playhouse Theme/A. Copeland/Victor Quan-Studio Center."
    - Shape of the River, open reel audio tape (Box 1045, Folder 1)
      On container, "PH 90/Shape of the River/I."
    - Dream of Treason, open reel audio tape (Box 1045, Folder 2)
      On container, "PH 90/#59-9-3/Dream of Treason/Good Takes."
  - Promise -- Papers, Subseries 139.
    A Hallmark Hall of Fame presentation.
    - Cast and Production Credits, 1986 November 11; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 17)
      Page one of two.
  - Quarterback Princess -- Papers, Subseries 140.
    Production no. 0310-3211-0979. Plot: The Maida family has moved to Oregon, and daughter Tami wants to play quarterback for the high school football team.
    - Post Production Schedule no. 1, 1983 August 24; 2 pages (Box 1860, Folder 18)
  - Quarterback Princess -- Scores, Subseries 258.
    - Full Score, 1983-1984; manuscript score (Box 94)
      Show no.: 3211-0979.
  - Quarterback Princess -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 141.
    Production no. 0310-3211-0979.
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 27, 1983; 2 in. tape (Box 996, Folder 1)
      On container, "QBack Princess/R-1/16 Trk/Non Dolby/15 IPS Scoring."
    - Coach's Speeches, August 6, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1055, Folder 22)
      On container, "0979/"QTR Back Princess"/Coaches Speeches/6 Aug 83."
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 2, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1055, Folder 23)
      On container, "Roll #2/"1/4 Back Princess"/#0979."
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 2, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1055, Folder 24)
      On container, "Roll #3/"1/4 B. Princess"/0979."
    - [Contents Unidentified], August 8, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1055, Folder 29)
      On container, "Roll #3A/8-8-83/#0979/Playback."
    - Logs 3979-4015, October 27, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1073, Folder 11)
      On container, "CED/10-27-83/R180/Logs 3979-4015/"Quarterback Princess"."
    - Logs 4016-4043, October 28, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1073, Folder 12)
      On container, "CED/10-28-83/R181/Logs 4016-4043/"Quarterback Princess"."
    - Logs 4044-4067, October 28, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1073, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/10-28-83/R182/Logs 4044-4067/"Quarterback Princess"."
    - Logs 4068-4075, October 28, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1073, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/10-28-83/R183/Logs 4068-4075/"Quarterback Princess"."
    - Logs 3979-4015, October 27, 1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1073, Folder 15)
      On container, "CED/10-27-83/R135/Logs 3979-4015/"Quarterback Princess"."
    - Logs 4016-4043, October 28, 1983; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1073, Folder 16)
      On container, "CED/10-28-83/R136/Logs 4016-4043/"Quarterback Princess"."
    - Logs 4068-4076, October 28, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1074, Folder 16)
      On container, "CED/10-28-83/R138/Logs 4068-4076/"Quarterback Princess"."
    - Logs 4044-4067, October 28, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1074, Folder 17)
      On container, "CED/10-28-83/R137/Logs 4044-4067/"Quarterback Princess"."
  - The Reckoning -- Recording Logs, Subseries 142.
    - Last Night of August, August 25, 1959 (Box 1170, Folder 8)
      Title taken from title page. On item, "Last Night of August / Re-Run / Prod. #59-8-34 / Music Log sent: 25 Aug. '59 / ? See original - Pursuit "The last Night of August" - 16 Dec. '58."
  - The Reckoning -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 143.
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1/4 in. tape (Box 1145, Folder 4)
      On container, "Reckoning ?/"B" Reel/21."
  - The Red Spider -- Papers, 1988 February 18-19; Subseries 144.; 7 sound recordings
    Production no. 0310-3560-0101. Plot: A cop is found dead in a hotel, brutally murdered, a spider cut into his stomach.
    - Post Production Schedule no. 3, 1988 January 28; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 21)
  - The Red Spider -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 145.
    - Logs 8003-8034, 1988 February 18; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1079, Folder 5)
      On container, "CED/2-18-88/R379/Logs 8003-8034/"Red Spider"."
    - Logs 8035-8062, 1988 February 19; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1079, Folder 6)
      On container, "CED/2-19-88/R380/Logs 8035-8062/"The Red Spider"."
    - Logs 8063-8068, 1988 February 19; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1079, Folder 7)
      On container, "CED/2-19-88/R381/Logs 8063-8068+DD's/"Red Spider"."
    - Logs 8003-8034, 1988 February 18; open reel audio tape (Box 1102, Folder 9)
      On container, "CED/12-18-88/R360/LOGS 8003-8034/"Red Spider"."
    - Logs 8035-8062, 1988 February 19; open reel audio tape (Box 1102, Folder 10)
      On container, "CED/2-19-88/R361/LOGS 8035-8062/"Red Spider"."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1988 February 18; open reel audio tape (Box 1105, Folder 9)
      On container, "CBS/Artie Kane/The Red Spider/2-18-88/Reel 2."CBS/Artie Kane/The Red Spider/2-18-88/Reel 2."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1988 February 18; open reel audio tape (Box 1105, Folder 11)
      On container, "CBS/Artie Kane/The Red Spider/2-18-88/Reel 1."
  - Relentless -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 146.
    - Logs 1149-1168, May 23, 1977; open reel audio tape (Box 1107, Folder 3)
      On container, "CTN/5-23-77/R49/LOGS 1149-1168/"Relentless"."
    - Logs 1169-1187, May 23-24, 1977; open reel audio tape (Box 1107, Folder 4)
      On container, "CTN/5-23-77, 5-24-77/R50/LOGS 1169-1187/"Relentless"."
    - Logs 1188-1200, May 24, 1977; open reel audio tape (Box 1107, Folder 5)
      On container, "CTN/5-24-77/R51/LOGS 1188-1200/"Relentless"."
    - Logs 1201-1209, May 24, 1977; open reel audio tape (Box 1107, Folder 6)
      On container, "CTN/5-24-77/R52/LOGS 1201-1209/"Relentless"."
  - The Return of Sherlock Holmes -- Papers, Subseries 147.
    Production no. 0310-2932-0319. Plot: Sherlock Holmes is brought back to life by Watson's female decendent after being cryogentically frozen for eighty years.
    - Movies on the CBS Television Network Notice, 1986 November 11; 3 pages (Box 1860, Folder 21)
      Description of the television movie featuring Margaret Colin and Michael Pennington.
    - Post Production Schedule no. 3, 1986 October 6; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 21)
  - The Return of Sherlock Holmes -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 148.
    - [Contents Unidentified], November 7, 1986; 2 in. tape (Box 1024, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS/208/Return of S. Holmes/11-7-86."
    - Logs 6452-6483, November 7, 1986; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1072, Folder 2)
      On container, "CED/11-7-86/R346/Logs 6452-6483/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6484-6511, November 7, 1986; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1072, Folder 3)
      On container, "CED/11-7-86/R347/Logs 6484-6511+DD/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6390-6404, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/11-6-86/R324/Logs 6390-6404/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6405-6428, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 7)
      On container, "CBS/11-6-86/R325/Logs 6405-6428/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6452-6483, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 8)
      On container, "CBS/11-6-86/R327/Logs 6452-6483/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6429-6451, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 9)
      On container, "CBS/11-6-86/R326/Logs 6429-6451/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6484-6508, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS/11-6-86/R328/Logs 6484-6508/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6429-6451, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 11)
      On container, "CED/11-6-86/R345/Logs 6429-6451/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6405-6428, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 12)
      On container, "CED/11-6-86/R344/Logs 6405-6428/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Logs 6389-6404, November 6, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/11-6-86/R343/Logs 6389-6404/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - [Contents Unidentified], open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 14)
      On container, "M44,53,73,M80,33/(Rick Marvin)Source Cues/"Return of Sherlock Holmes"."
    - Louie, Louie, open reel audio tape (Box 1090, Folder 15)
    - Hari Krishna, open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 20)
      On container, "M-44."
    - Hari Krishna, open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 20)
      On container, "M-44/"Sherlock Holmes""Hari Krishna"."
  - Run Till You Fall -- Papers, Subseries 149.
    Production no. 0310-3554-0101.
    - Post Production Schedule, 1987 October 21; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 21)
    - Post Production Schedule no. 1, 1987 October 21; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 21)
  - Run Till You Fall -- Scripts, Subseries 150.
    - Run Till You Fall, 83 p. (Box 1819, Folder 6)
  - Run 'Till You Fall -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 151.
    - Logs 7021-7041, November 5, 1987; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1078, Folder 19)
      On container, "CED/11-5-87/R364/LOGS 7021-7041/"Run Till You Fall"."
    - Logs 7041-7061, November 5, 1987; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1081, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/11-5-87/R365/LOGS 7042-7061+7041 Edit/"Run Till You Fall"."
    - Logs 7000-7020, November 5, 1987; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1109, Folder 12)
      On container, "CED/11-5-87/R347/LOGS 7000-7020/"Run Till You Fall"."
    - Logs 7021-7041, November 5, 1987; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1109, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/11-5-87/R348/LOGS 7021-7041/"Run Till You Fall"."
    - Logs 7042-7061, November 5, 1987; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1109, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/11-5-87/R349/LOGS 7042-7061/"Run Till You Fall"."
    - Logs 7000-7020, November 5, 1987; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1109, Folder 15)
      On container, "CED/11-5-87/R363/LOGS 7000-7020/"Run Till You Fall"."
    - Run "Til You Fall, Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
    - Run 'Til You Fall, Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
    - Run 'Til You Fall., Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
      Tape contains: The Late Show -- Silent Partner -- Alfred Hitchcock -- Tribute.
    - Run 'Til You Fall., Cassette tape.. (Box 1851)
      Tape contains: Maddie's Blues-Moonlighting -- Stargaze -- Three Sounds For Jazz Orchestra -- Ballad For Gary -- Just Feelin' So Blue.
    - Run 'Til You Fall., Cassette tape. (Box 1851)
      Both sides are netitled "Jazz."
  - Running Out == Papers
    - Recording logs, 1982 (Box 1561)
  - Running Out -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 152.
    - Logs 3074-3077, September 20, 1982; open reel tape (Box 1044, Folder 9)
      On container, "CED/9-20-82/R133/Logs 3074-3077/Running Out."
    - Logs 3074-3077, September 20, 1982; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1052, Folder 5)
      On container, "CED/9-20-82/R86/Logs 3074-3077/"Running Out"."
    - Logs 3045-3067, September 20, 1982; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1052, Folder 6)
    - Logs 3071-3073, September 20, 1982; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1052, Folder 6)
    - Log 3325, January 10, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1068, Folder 3)
      On container, "CED/1-10-83/logs 3360-3372, 3325, song/"Running Out"."
    - Logs 3360-3372, January 10, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1068, Folder 3)
    - Logs 3334-3359, January 10, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1068, Folder 4)
      On container, "CED/1-10-83/R150/logs 3334-3359/"Running Out"."
    - Logs 3318-3333, January 10, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1068, Folder 5)
      On container, "CED/1-10-83/R149/logs 3318-3333/"Running Out"."
    - Log 3325, January 10, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1068, Folder 6)
      On container, "CED/1-10-83/R105/logs 3360, 3372, 3325, song/"Running Out"."
    - Log 3360, January 10, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1068, Folder 6)
    - Log 3372, January 10, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1068, Folder 6)
    - Logs 3334-3359, January 10, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1068, Folder 7)
      On container, "CED/ 1-10-83/ R104/logs 3334-3359/"Running Out"."
    - Logs 3318-3333, January 10, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1068, Folder 8)
      On container, "CED/1-10-83/logs 3318-3333/"Running Out"."
  - Scarlet Pimpernel -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 153.
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1982 September 29; 6 tapes (Box 1052, Folder 4)
      On container, "London Films/29-9-82/Scarlet Pimpernel/Reel 1."
  - Scrooge -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 154.
    - [Contents Unidentified], open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 8)
    - Logs 1-2, 1970 January 9; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1128, Folder 13)
      On container, "CCF/1-19-70/R55A/LOGS 1-2/#5077-0000/Scrooge."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1/4 in. tape (Box 1147, Folder 2)
      On container, "Cinema Center Films "Scrooge"/Stereo 15 - copy."
  - The Secret Adventures of Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn -- Papers
    - Recording logs, 1982 (Box 1559)
    - Recording logs, 1982 (Box 1560)
  - The Secret Adventures of Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 155.
    - Logs 2188-2210, 1982 January 7; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1027, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/1-7-82/R47/Logs 2188-2210/Tom Sawyer + Huck Finn."
    - Logs 2211-2225, 1982 January 7; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1027, Folder 2)
      On container, "CED/1-7-82/R48/Logs 2211-2225/Tom Sawyer + Huck Finn."
    - Logs 2226-2255, 1982 January 8; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1027, Folder 3)
      On container, "CED/1-8-82/R49/Logs 2226-2255/Tom Sawyer + Huck Finn."
    - Logs 2171-2187, 1982 January 7; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1027, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/1-7-82/R46/Logs 2171-2187/Secret Adventures of Tom Sawyer + Huck Finn."
    - Logs 2286-2310, 1982 January 8; 1/2" tape (Box 1056, Folder 12)
      On container, "CED/1-8-82/R51/logs 2286-2310/"Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn"."
    - Logs 2226-2310, 1982 January 7 - 1982 January 8; open reel audio tape (Box 1056, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/1-7-82/1-8-82/R98/(printtakes only)/logs 2226-2310/Tom Sayer and Huck Finn."
    - Logs 2171-2225, 1982 January 7; open reel audio tape (Box 1056, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/1-7-82/R97/printtakes only/logs 2171-2225/Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn."
    - Logs 2256-2285, 1982 January 8; 1/2" tape (Box 1056, Folder 15)
      On container, "CED/1-8-82/R 50/logs 2256-2285/Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn."
  - Secrets of a Mother and Daughter -- Papers, Subseries 156.
    - Movies on the CBS Television Network Notice, 1986 July 30; 2 pages (Box 1860, Folder 22)
      Describes the CBS Sunday movie scheduled to air on September 7, 1986 featuring Katharine Ross, Linda Hamilton and Michael Nouri.
  - Shakedown on the Sunset Stip -- Papers, Subseries 267.
    Alternate title: Vice Queen of the Sunset Strip.
    - Scripts, 1987 April 20-27; 49 p. (Box 1819, Folder 7)
      May be incomplete. Production no. 0310-3556-0101.
    - Post Production Schedule no. 2, 1987 July 1; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 26)
      Production no. 0310-3556-0101.
    - Staff and Crew List, 1987 April 27; 2 pages (Box 1860, Folder 26)
  - Shakedown on the Sunset Strip -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 157.
    - Logs 6690-6724, 1987 August 13; open reel audio tape (Box 1069, Folder 16)
      On container, "CBS/8-13-87/R338/Logs 6690-6724/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6667-6689, 1987 August 13; open reel audio tape (Box 1069, Folder 17)
      On container, "CBS/8-13-87/R337/Logs 6667-6689/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6747-6772, 1987 August 14; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1094, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS/8-14-87/R356/Logs 6747-6772/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6773-6787, 1987 August 14; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1094, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS/8-14-87/R357/Logs 6773-6787/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6725-6746, 1987 August 13; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1099, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS/8-13-97/R355/Logs 6725-6746/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6724-6790, 1987 August 13; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1099, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS/8-13-87/R354/Logs 6790-6724/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6667-6724, 1987 August 13; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1099, Folder 3)
      On container, "CBS/8-13-87/R353/Logs 6667-6724/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6725-6746, 1987 August 13; open reel audio tape (Box 1099, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/8-13-87/R339/Logs 6725-6746/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6773-6787, 1987 August 14; open reel audio tape (Box 1099, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/8-14-87/R341/Logs 6773-6787/"Shakedown on the Sunset Strip"."
    - Logs 6747-6772, 1987 August 14; open reel audio tape (Box 1099, Folder 6)